(电话的铃声)
(ringing of the phone)
本:你好,这里是本*希佛家.开萝尔,找你的,你那傻子男朋友.
Ben: Hello Ben siever's residence.Carol, it's your stupid boyfriend.
开萝尔:闭上你的嘴,别吭声儿.电话挂了,本.
Carol: Shut up Ben, just shut up.Hang up the phone Ben.
杰森:本,你妈妈还没到家么?
Jason: Ben, is your mom home yet?
本:没.
Ben: Nope.
杰森:我刚才好像听到她车的声音了.
Jason: I thought I heard her car.
本:那是迈克.他刚洗完车,
Ben: That's Mike.He just washed his car and he's driving it back and forth
在马路上来回开,想把车晾晾干.
in the driveway to air dry it.
杰森:最好她能快点回来,否则我们看电影就晚了.
Jason: Well she better hurry up or we're going to miss the start of that movie.
本:我真不明白你们为什么喜欢周五晚上看电影,其实你们可以呆在家里看电视,
Ben: I don't get why you guys want to spend Friday night at a movie when
周五晚上放的电视是一周中最棒的.
you could stay home with me on the best TV night of the week.
杰森:是这样的本.
Jason: Well, it's like this Ben.
每隔一段时间呢,我和你妈妈希望能够有机会出去独处,
Every once in a while your mom and I like to go out alone together just
以庆贺我们有三个可爱的孩子.
to celebrate the fact that we have three great kids.
本:真的么,爸爸.
Ben: Sure dad.
杰森:另外,周二晚上的电视才是一周中最好的.哦,本 ,
Jason: Besides Tuesday night is the best TV night and oh Ben,
今晚这儿还有一个新的看小孩儿的,那,对她好点儿,好么?
this is a new sitter tonight so please be kind to her, ok?
本:不要看小孩儿的!
Ben: I don't need a sitter!
杰森:我们已经决定了.
Jason: We've been over that.
本:我的意思是说,跟开萝尔约会那男的今不来了,所以开萝尔可以看我.
Ben: I just mean that the guy taking out Carol out cancelled so she can watch me.
杰森:我就想希望我能找着那个看小孩儿的.
Jason: Well I just hope that I can catch the sitter!
开萝尔:我在打电话呢
Carol: I'm on the phone pea brain!
麦琪:嗨,亲爱的,嗨,本.
Maggie: Hi honey, hi Ben
杰森:……
Jason: TGIF
麦琪:哦,你说过的,我就想把脚放高了歇会儿.
Maggie: Oh you said it, I just want to put my feet up and relax .
本:妈妈,你忘了还有场电影呢.
Ben: Mom, you forgot the movie.
麦琪:什么电影?
Maggie: What movie?
本:就是爸爸一整周都朝思暮想的那场电影.
Ben: The one dad's been looking forward to all week.
杰森:没关系的,本.我们呆在家里跟你在一起,一样会很开心的.
Jason: Well that's ok, Ben, we'll have just as much fun staying at home with you.
本:还有开萝尔.
Ben: And Carol .
麦琪:那她和博比*维耐特的约会,出了什么事?
Maggie: What happened to her date with Bobby Winette?
本:他被关起来了.
Ben: He's grounded
迈克:我没有做什么错事啊.
Mike: I didn't do anything.
本:说的是开萝尔的男朋友,六个月里这是他第三张开车超速的罚单.
Ben: It's Carol's boyfriend.He got his third speeding ticket in 6 months.
迈克:这下好了博比!呣,总得有人跟这孩子说两句话吧.
Mike: Alright bobby!Umm, I mean, somebody should speak to the boy.
开萝尔:说坏消息.
Carol: Talk about bad news.
迈克:博比被关起来了,约会已经吹了,你呢也.我听说的.
Mike: Bobby's grounded, the date's cancelled, you're bummed.I heard.
好了,如果各位允许的话,失陪了,我得去冲个澡.
Now if you'll excuse me, I have to go shower.
麦琪:哦,今晚有大阴谋?
Maggie: Oh big plans tonight?
迈克:没,就我,埃迪还有鲍纳,准备去好好玩会儿.
Mike: No, just me, eddie, and Boner are going to go hang out.
杰森:你洗澡,为了埃迪和鲍纳?
Jason: You're going to shower for Eddie and Boner?
迈克:得了,爸爸,我洗个澡是因为,我可能有意外收获.
Mike: C'mon dad I'm showering cause I might get lucky.
麦琪:解释解释,什么叫意外收获?
Maggie: Define get lucky.
迈克:呣,是这样的,我,
Mike: Um, well, you know, I, uh,
阿,可能会撞上我的某位老师,而我呢肯定不想让他看到我脏兮兮的样子.
might run into one of my teachers and I sure want to be clean for that.
本:那家伙说过,他要去蹓达勾女人.
Ben: That buck said he's going patrolling for chicks.
麦琪:好了,
Maggie: Ok Ben, here's your beans and weenies,
本.吃你的豆和香肠.
and Carol you get the macho meat beef and Jason here's your ...
开萝尔,
it sure tastes like chicken chicken.
(电话响起)
(phone rings)
本:你好.对,迈克,是埃迪的电话.
Ben: Hello.Yeah.Mike it's Eddie.
迈克:问他有什么留言,我在刮着呢.
Mike: Take a message I'm shaving.
本:他在刮什么呢?
Ben: What's he shaving?
杰森:嗨,
Jason: Hey those two chins hairs can get kind of unruly.You know?
本:我会转告他的,埃迪.
Ben: I'll tell him Eddie.Eddie says what's keeping you?
埃迪问,你不能接电话是在干什么?
There's a thousand vices out there with your name on em.
杰森:好的,我会跟他谈的.
Jason: Yes, I'll have a talk with him.
麦琪:谢谢.
Maggie: Thank you.
迈克:呃,爸爸,
Mike: Uhh dad there's no need for you to have a talk with me after the
您确实没必要跟我谈什么,
fine job that you and dad have done teaching me the proper values,
你还有妈妈已经教育我正确的价值观,
I don't think there's going to be anything to worry about.
你们做得已经很不错了,我不觉得你们还能有什么不放心的.
I mean what can you do?Lock me in my room?
麦琪和杰森:呣--------.
Maggie and Jason: hmmmm.
迈克:嗨---
Mike: Heyyy.
开萝尔:我去接.
Carol: I'll get it.
迈克:好了,那我一点钟回来,
Mike: Okay so I'll see you guys at one and you know there's no need at
你们不用等我了.
all for You guys to wait up for me.
麦琪:轮到谁等了?你,还是我?
Maggie: So who's turn is it to wait up?Yours or mine?
特鲁迪:嗨!
Trudy: So like hi!
麦琪:杰森,你忘了退订看小孩儿的保姆了?
Maggie: Jason you forgot to cancel the babysitter?
杰森:我以为你已经退了呢.特鲁迪,
Jason: I thought you did.Trudy, I'm sorry but we changed our plans.
对不起,我们的计划改变了,我会送你回家的.
I'll run you home.
物鲁迪:哦,哇,我不让的.
Trudy: Oh wow, I'm not allowed.
杰森:对不起,我没听清?
Jason: Excuse me?
特鲁迪:我妈妈和爸爸今晚出去了,
Trudy: My mom and dad are out for the evening and I'm not allowed to be
他们不让我一个人呆家里.
home alone.
本:等会儿,让我挑明了吧, 我的保姆需要人看么?
Ben: Wait a minute here.Let me get this straight.My sitter needs a sitter?
迈克:那,你们这帮家伙想要干什么?
Mike: So what do you guys want to do?
鲍纳:呣,我们还想问你呢,你脑瓜99%都和别人不一样.
Boner: Umm, we could try the bowl your brains out 99 cent special.
埃迪:又来?
Eddie: Again?
鲍纳:那,你想到什么好主意了么?
Boner: Well you think of something?
鲍纳:USAN有一个少年组合.
Boner: Well USAN is having a teenage mixer and fish fry.
迈克:你们准备散伙.
Mike: You're having a break down.
埃迪:嗨,我明白了,我明白了.听着,我们可以我车停在外面,看电影!
Eddie: Hey, I got it, I got it.Look, we could go park outside a drive-in and lip read a movie!
鲍纳:好主意,这真是个好主意.
Boner: That's good, that's real good.
埃迪:来吧,伙计们,是瑞典片.
Eddie: C'mon man it's Swedish.
(大笑)
(laughing)
迈克:罗兰德*泰勒,嗨,伙计,还好么?
Mike: Roland Taylor, hey man, how you doing?
罗兰德:很好.希佛,埃迪,鲍纳,最近怎么样?
Roland: I'm good.Siever.Eddie, Boner, how's it going?
埃迪:上大学的事怎么样了?
Eddie: How's college?
迈克:甭提了,你呢?
Mike: Forget college, how's the co-ed dorm?
鲍纳:那,你一直在做什么?
Boner: So what have you been up to?
罗兰德:买点比萨,我们有个小聚会.你们呢?
Roland: Just picking up some pizzas for a little get-together.You?
迈克:哦,我们有大事,大事.我们今晚约了几个瑞典女孩.
Mike: Oh big stuff, big stuff.We've got some dates with some Swedish women tonight.
罗兰德:祝今晚我们都马到成功.很高兴见得你们,伙计们.
Roland: Tonight's working out for all of us.It's good to see you guys
迈克:你也一样.
Mike: You too.
埃迪:伙计,他找到什么事儿做了?
Eddie: Man, what's he got going?
比萨店女孩:8个大比萨,总共74.55块.
Pizza Girl: 8 large pizzas.That's 74.55.
罗兰德:没关系,零钱给你了.
Roland: Ok you keep the change.
迈克:嗨,罗兰德,这就是今晚的小聚会.
Mike: Hey Roland so about this little get-together tonight.
罗兰德:就是你们的标准,年青的姑娘,
Roland: It's just your standard.
父母都不在身边,咱们今晚好好玩玩儿.
Young girls, heated pool, no parents let's get crazy event.
埃迪:好哇你罗兰德!谁我帮你一把.来,帮帮这兄弟.
Eddie: Yo ROLANDO!Let me give you a hand here.C'mon help the man out.
罗兰德:好.等,等会儿.你们真得可怜到这个地步了么,几乎是在求着我参加这个party?
Roland: Fine.Wait, wait a minute are you guys really so pathetic that you're practically begging me to come to the party?
男孩们:对!
Boys: yes!
罗兰德:好的,吃的在那边,
Roland: Ok, the food's over there,
喝的在那边,而女人呢,到处都是.
the drinks are over there and the women are, what the heck, everywhere.
迈克:嗨,罗兰德,这房子到底是谁的?
Mike: Hey rols so who's house is this anyway?
罗兰德:我也不知道.
Roland: Beats me.
鲍纳:要不你先查看一下这个地方?
Boner: Will you look at this place?
迈克:好,我是观察员.
Mike: Yeah, I'm looking man.
埃迪:天哪,看那边,钢琴旁,那不是杜威高中毕业的兰娜么?
Eddie: Holy, look over there by the piano.Is that Lana from Dewey?
鲍纳:兰娜是谁?
Boner: Lana who?
埃迪:兰娜,
Eddie: Lana my daddy gave me a porche for my birthday Fairday..
鲍纳:等,也没准儿是.我从来没跟她在同一个房间过.
Boner: Wait that could be.I've never been in the same room as her.
迈克:哦,看,伙计们.还有艾米和彼得,还有乔*辛普森.你们能相信么,我们跟他们这帮人同在一个party上?
Mike: Oh look man.There's Emmy and peter.Wait that's joe simpson.Can you actually believe we're at the same party as these guys?
鲍纳:对,你说得对,我们应该走了.
Boner: Yeah you're right we should go.
迈克:不,别磨蹭了,我们没有理由和这帮人处不好,对不对?冷静点,别激动.
Mike: No, c'mon there's no reason why we can not run with this hight crowd, right?Just stay cool .
鲍纳:哇,兄弟们怎么不看一看这个大妈?
Boner: Wow would guys take a look at this momma?
迈克:冷静点,鲍纳,冷静.这真的是一个经典的聚会!
Mike: Cool it Boner, cool it.C'mon this is a real classy bunch!
女孩:对不起.
Girl: Excuse me.
埃迪:先生们,你们开足马力,我得先去趟洗手间.
Eddie: Gentlemen, start your engines.I gotta go to the john first.
其它兄弟们,嗨,排队.
Other guy hey wait your turn bozo.
埃迪:哦,对不起.
Eddie: Oh sorry.
鲍纳:嗨,你们没有注意到么?富人们去洗手间都是成群结队的.
Boner: Hey did you guys notice something?Rich people go to the bathroom in groups.
迈克:你是怎么知道这个的呢?得了,
Mike: Why didn't you know that?
别在人家面前让我们大家没面子了,鲍纳.
C'mon don't embarrass us in front of these people Boner.
埃迪:失陪,那小姑娘找我.
Eddie: Excuse me, that chick wants me.
迈克:来,动真格的.
Mike: C'mon get real
鲍纳:不,她找的是我.
Boner: No, she wants me.
迈克:好了,你们几个争吧,呃,嗨,对不起打扰一下,我是想说你看起来太美了就像影星.
Mike: Alright well you guys discuss it uh, hi, um I'm sorry but I just had to tell you that you look just like a movie star
女孩:真的么?哪个影星?
Girl: Really?Which one?
迈克:哪个影星?就那个非常性感的影星,你知道的.
Mike: Which one?Well, you know that real sexy movie star.
女孩:拉伯*劳维?
Girl: Robb lowe?
迈克:对!不,不……
Mike: Right!No, no...
女孩:你倒有点挺可爱的噢.
Girl: You're kind of cute
迈克:对,不过这只是假象.
Mike: Yeah, well it's a look.
女孩:那,呃,你愿意去洗手间么,和我一起?
Girl: So, uh, would you like to go to the john with me?
迈克:哈哈哈,呃,不不,没关系的,你去吧.
Mike: Hahaha, uh, no, no, it's okay you go.
女孩:哦,对不起.你以为我
Girl: Oh sorry, you probably think that I'm after your stash.
迈克:啊?
Mike: Huh?
女孩:免费的,呃,你很帅,不是么?
Girl: It's my treat.Uh you are cool, aren't you?
迈克:呣,爽,好的.
Mike: Um cool.Yeah.
女孩:该我们了.
Girl: Our turn.
迈克:呃,听着,我得去洗手间了.
Mike: Uh listen, I gotta go to the bathroom.
女孩:好啊!
Girl: Right!
迈克:不,我不是指那个洗手间,我是指这个洗手间.
Mike: No I don't mean the bathroom, I mean the bathroom.
兰娜:罗兰德,你父母在电话上呢,是长途.
Lana: Rhonda your parents are on the phone long distance.
女孩:好了,嗯,不要走嘛.
Girl: Ok, um, don't go away.
兰娜:迈克 *希佛,是么?
Lana: Mike Siever, right?
迈克:呃,是我!兰娜,你不知道,见到你我有多高兴.
Mike: Uh yeah!Lana you have no idea how nice it is to see you.
兰娜:啊!我见到你也很高兴.
Lana: Ah!Nice to see you too.
迈克:你看,兰娜,别害怕,不过我要提醒你这聚会上有海洛因.
Mike: Look lana, don't freak but there is cocaine at this party.
兰娜:(笑)那好啊,我正想要呢!你真就意思!别害怕.好哇,好哇.
Lana: (laughs) Well, I should hope so!You're funny!Don't freak.That's great, that's great.
迈克:兄弟们,兄弟们,你们知不知道这是个什么样的聚会?
Mike: Guys, guys do you have any idea what kind of party this is?
鲍纳:哦,知道,这是个很好的聚会.
Boner: Oh yeah, it's a great one.
迈克:不,不是的,兄弟,绝对不是.听好了,这聚会上有海洛因.就在那儿,厕所里.
Mike: No it's not man, it's not.Listen there's cocaine at this party.Right there in that bathroom.
埃迪:哇,这么回事啊,
Eddie: Wow.So rich people don't necessarily go to the bathroom together
看来富人们也不一定是上厕所都成群结队的喽!
after all!
迈克:得了,兄弟们,现在我问你们,咱们对海洛因没兴趣,是不是?
Mike: C'mon guys now we're not really interested in cocaine are we?
男孩们:我没兴趣,我没兴趣.
Boys: Not me, not me
迈克:那咱们离开这个鬼地方.
Mike: Let's get the hell out of here.
埃迪:可是,我对兰娜感兴趣.
Eddie: But I am interested in Lana.
鲍纳:哦,耶.
Boner: Oh yeah.
迈克:兰娜?她抽海洛因,兄弟,我觉得她是上瘾了.
Mike: Lana?She does cocaine too, man.I thought she was cool.
鲍纳:好了,迈克 ,很多人都用海洛因的.
Boner: Well Mike a lot of cool people use cocaine.
迈克:得了,海洛因能致人于死地的.
Mike: C'mon that stuff is killing people .
埃迪:海洛因不会伤害我们的,如果我们就用一次,
Eddie: It's not going to hurt us if we use it just one time with lana
和兰娜还有她的女伴儿们.
and her female friends.
鲍纳:对.
Boner: Yeah.
迈克:听着,兄弟们,
Mike: Look guys I'm sure that everybody's who been screwed up with that
最后上瘾的人最初都这么想的.
drug felt the same way that first time.
鲍纳:对,你是说我们是想要成瘾么.
Boner: Yeah, you're saying we're that wishy washy.
埃迪:对!
Eddie: Yeah!
迈克:你能不能看看那个人?如果是我,我就不干.得了,咱们散伙吧.
Mike: Would you look at the man?I rest my case.C'mon let's split.
鲍纳:迈克,如果我们这么走,大家都会觉得我们是胆小怕事的人.
Boner: Mike everyone's going to think we're weenies if we go.
迈克:不,他们不会的,兄弟,听好了,这些人有谁认识我们.我们偷偷地溜出去,又有谁会知道呢?
Mike: No they won't man, look, none of these people even know us.We can just slip out of here and who will know?
罗兰德;嗨,希佛!我刚刚又找到了六个杜威的啦啦队.
Roland: Hey Siever!I found six more dewey hooters here tonight.
女孩:嗨,迈克!
Girl: Hi Mike!
迈克:嗨噢,好嘛.
Mike: Hi oh good.
(电视噪音)
(TV noise)
麦琪:谁还想再来点苹果派?
Maggie: Who wants some fresh from the oven mock apple pie.
所有人:嘘-----!
Everyone: Shhhh!
麦琪:亲爱的,苹果.
Maggie: Honey, mock apple.
杰森:好的.
Jason: Sure.
本:妈妈,卡特尔使用骡子运送半吨的未提炼的毒品通过迈阿密.我们说的是,市价1600万元.
Ben: Mom, the cartel has their mules running a half a ton of uncut snow through the Miami pipeline.We're talking the street value of 16 million big ones here.
特鲁迪:好俗啊.
Trudy: Sounds low to me.
麦琪:好了,我有一个好主意.为什么不看看迪斯尼电影磁带呢?
Maggie: Well I've got a great idea.Why don't we watch a Disney movie on tape?
杰森:耶!
Jason: Yeah!
本:妈妈,不看,特鲁迪在跟前不看.
Ben: Mom, not in front of Trudy.
麦琪:那,灰姑娘怎么样么?灰姑娘和那些可爱的小老鼠?
Maggie: How about Cinderella with those cute, little mice?
开萝尔:去年我们看老鼠的时候,你可没有觉得它们可爱.
Carol: When we had mice last year you didn't think they were so cute.
杰森:麦琪,我吃的到底是什么?味道像是馊了的饼什么的.
Jason: Maggie, exactly what am I eating?This tastes like a soggy cracker or something.
特鲁迪:那是我爸爸.
Trudy: That's my dad.
麦琪:好了,特鲁迪,有你这样的客人我们很荣幸.
Maggie: Well Trudy it's been nice having you as our guest.
特鲁迪:客人?你们是不打算付我工钱了么?
Trudy: Guest?Does that mean you're going to try to get out of paying me?
麦琪:呃,当然不是了.杰森,你说呢?
Maggie: Uh, uh of course not.Jason?
杰森:哦,杰森,耶,不然不是否.这样的,特鲁迪.这个给你.
Jason: Oh Jason yeah right.Sure.Here Trudy.Here you go.
特鲁迪:谢谢.如果您什么时候还需要我给您看孩子请告诉我.
Trudy: Thanks.Any time you want me to baby-sit you guys just let me know.
杰森:好的.
Jason: Ok.
麦琪:当我还是小姑娘的时候,这是我最喜爱的电影.
Maggie: Now this was my favorite movie when I was a little girl.
开萝尔:哦,天,我累了.
Carol: Oh boy am I tired.
本:耶,累的是我,晚安,爸爸,晚安,妈妈.
Ben: Yeah, I'm one tired, little puppy good night dad, good night mom.
麦琪:晚安.
Maggie: Good night.
杰森:我十岁的时候,如果能知道现在的本所知道的一半,那我会变得非常危险.
Jason: Boy, when I was 10 if I knew half of what Ben knows now I'd have been Dangerous.
麦琪:亲爱的,本已经够危险的了.
Maggie: Honey Ben is dangerous.
(音乐)
(Music)
女孩:嗨,迈克.
Girl: Hi Mike.
迈克:嗨.
Mike: Hi.
埃迪:我们完了,我们完了,大家都会认为我们是胆小鬼的.
Eddie: We're dead, we're dead.Everyone's going to think we're weenies.
鲍纳:也不一不定,
Boner: Not necessarily, I've got an idea.
我有一个主意.咱们别说我们不想尝试海洛因,
We don't say that we don't want to try cocaine.
只说咱们在十点钟前必须到家.
All we have to say is that we have to be home before 10.
迈克:这有什么好玩的?
Mike: What's so funny?
兰娜:我还以为,
Lana: I was just thinking how upset my mom and dad would be if they knew
我爸爸妈妈知道我参加这个party会有多么多么的不开心呢.
I was having this party.
迈克:怎么了?
Mike: What?
兰娜:你看,他们也抽.好了,刚才我们到哪儿了?
Lana: Well you see it's their coke.Now where were we?
迈克:呃,这样的,我刚才是想说……
Mike: Uh look, I just wanted to say ...
埃迪:他是想说这位是埃迪,那位是鲍纳.
Eddie: That I'm Eddie and that's boner up there.
女孩:嗨,咱们一块儿吧.兰娜!
Girl: Hi well let's make this a group tooth.Lana!
罗兰德:埃迪,希佛,现在你们可以很爽,或者,也可以做个软蛋,呃?
Roland: Eddie, Siever, now you can be cool or you can be a wimp here huh?
兰娜:啊----,这个热盆看起来太棒了.
Lana: Ahhh, that hot tub is looking pretty good.
女孩:如果去洗手间一趟,它看起来会更棒的确.兰娜,如果我做,不介意吧.
Girl: It will look better once we visit the bathroom.Lana don't mind if I do.
埃迪:哦,热桶,跟兰娜*菲尔迪一起,我真受不了了!真走运我还穿了一件裤子,我干净的内衣都用完了.
Eddie: Oh hotubbing with Lana Fairday, I can't stand it! It's lucky I'm wearing my trunks.I ran out of clean underwear!
兰娜:我们,可以么?
Lana: Shall we?
鲍纳:不用给我们迈克吹,呃?
Boner: Don't blow this for us Mike huh?
女孩:那他,呃,哪儿有问题?
Girl: Is, uh, something wrong?
迈克:呣,听着,我没心情,好了吧.
Mike: Um look I'm just not in the mood okay.
鲍纳:对,他这会儿正想把所有的药都从身体里清除掉呢.
Boner: Yeah, he's trying to get all the heavy drugs out of his system.
男孩:怎么着都行,如果你们想商量一下,
Boy: Anyway, please, if you guys are going to have a discussion can we
我们可不可以用一下洗手间?
use the john?
兰娜:先等会儿,好么?这儿到底是怎么回事?
Lana: Just wait a minute okay?Now what's going on here?
迈克:呣,这样的,我从来没用过海洛因.
Mike: Um, look I've never done coke before.
兰娜:刚才有那么一会儿,我还以为你们很棒!尤其是那个模样怪怪的.
Lana: For a second there I thought you guys were narcs!Especially the strange Looking one.
鲍纳:谢谢.
Boner: Thank you
女孩:听好了,如果这是你们第一次,我们会温柔点的.
Girl: Look, if it's your first time we'll be gentle with you.
鲍纳:第一次.
Boner: First time
埃迪:耶,第一次.
Eddie: Yeah first time.
迈克:嗨,我不想用海洛因,不可以么?
Mike: Hey, I don't want to do coke ok?
女孩们(格格笑)
Girls (giggling)
迈克:那有什么好笑的么?
Mike: C'mon what's wrong with that?
女孩:呣,我想去看看热桶怎么样了.
Girl: Umm, I'm gonna go check on the hot tub.
兰娜:我跟你一块去.
Lana: I'll come with you.
男孩:失陪了,伙计们.
Boy: Excuse us boys.
迈克:兄弟们,我感觉你是地狱,
Mike: Guys I feel like a jerk, let's get out of here.
咱们走吧.你们走还是不走啊?
Are you guys coming or what?
埃迪:得了,迈克 ,她正在检查热桶呢!
Eddie: C'mon Mike she's checking on the hot tub!
迈克:埃迪,走不走?
Mike: Eddie can we go?
鲍纳:投票决定,呃.
Boner: Let's put it to a vote, huh.
迈克:听着,我们一块儿来,我们应该一块儿走.
Mike: Look, we came together we should leave together.
我认为你俩是我的朋友.好了,你们可以走,也可以留,
I thought you guys were my friends.
随便,但是,我要走了.
Alright, you guys can stay or you can go, but I'm leaving.
埃迪:我想留,迈克.
Eddie: I think I want to stay Mike.
迈克:鲍纳?
Mike: Boner?
鲍纳:迈克,朋友不会迫使朋友做他们不愿意做的事情.
Boner: Mike, friends don't make friends do something they don't want to.
迈克:一点儿没错.
Mike: Exactly
埃迪:我从来没想到希佛会胆小成那样.
Eddie: You know, I never thought Siever would wimp out like that.
鲍纳:什么?你有点犯迷糊,
Boner: What?You're confused man.
兄弟.我们和迈克从一年级时就在一起了,他不是个胆小鬼,
We've been running with Mikey since the first grade.We know he's not a wimp.
咱们都清楚.他很冷静.
He's cool.
兰娜:好了,你们是进来呢,还是出去?
Lana: So, are you in or are you out, boys?
杰森:已经2点钟了,真是个美妙的夜晚.
Jason: Well it's 2 am.That's a nice night.
迈克:爸爸!
Mike: Dad!
杰森:迈克?那是迈克,是不是?
Jason: Mike?It is Mike, right?No, it couldn't be.
不,不可能.迈克应该1点钟就已经到家
My Mike was supposed to be home at 1 am.
迈克:呃,爸爸 ,我没能按时回家睡觉.
Mike: Uh dad, I know I missed my curfew.
杰森:至少,你还承认自己有不按时回家睡觉的时候,有进步啊.
Jason: Whoa, at least you admitted you had one.Now that's progress.
迈克:嗨,爸爸 ,
Mike: Hey dad, isn't tonight the night we turn the clocks back for the
时制变动,把时间回拨一小时,是今天晚上么?
time change?
杰森:不是,迈克,
Jason: No, Mike, that's in October which is when you're going to be grounded
那会在10月份,到那时候再不按时回家你就会被关起来,不给我一个合理解释就就别出来.
until unless you can give me a good explanation for where you've been.
迈克:好的.
Mike: ok,
杰森:不不不,等等等.让我在这儿舒服会儿,
Jason: No, no no wait, wait, wait, let me get comfortable here.
你知道我有多么地喜欢这些故事啊.今晚的会是什么呢,迈克?
You know how I love these stories.What will it be tonight, Mike?
你出去了,又救了几条人命?别走,
You were out and saved some lives tonight.
站住,我敢肯定你又去了那些地方?你没事吧?
No wait I'll bet you ran into those darn gypsies again.Are you okay?
迈克:爸爸,我能不能对你像朋友一样平等地交谈?
Mike: Dad, can I talk to you as a friend?
而不是一个整天让我难堪,让我日子不好过的一个什么人?
Not as a guy who will make my life miserable?
杰森:有什么不对么,迈克?
Jason: What's wrong Mike?
迈克:爸爸,我想确定,如果我跟你说了实话那你不会用来惩罚我.
Mike: Dad, I gotta know that what I tell you won't be used against me.
杰森:可以,什么事?
Jason: Okay, what is it?
迈克:好的,那就是说你已经答应我了无论我说什么你都不会……
Mike: Ok, so I have your word that whatever I say you're not going to...
杰森:迈克,少废话,行么?
Jason: Mike, just say it okay?
迈克:好好.我,埃迪还有鲍纳,我们三个无意中撞上了一个party,每一人都……都吸海洛因.
Mike: Ok.Me and Eddie and Boner.We ended up at a party where everybody was doing, doing cocaine.
杰森:海洛因?
Jason: Cocaine?
迈克:等,你不是我爸爸,你是一个朋友!
Mike: Wait, you're not my dad, you're a friend!
杰森:海洛因?真的么?
Jason: Cocaine?Really?
迈克:是的,如果你不吸,那你就是胆小鬼.
Mike: Yeah, and if you didn't do it you were a wimp.
杰森:海洛因.
Jason: Cocaine.
迈克:爸爸 ,我从来没感到有这么大的压力.
Mike: Dad I never felt so much pressure in my life.
杰森:还有?
Jason: And?
迈克:还有来自鲍纳和埃迪的压力.
Mike: And from boner and Eddie.
杰森:还有?
Jason: And?
迈克:还有,就像我根本就没有选择必须得那么做似的.
Mike: And it was like I didn't even have a choice.
杰森:还有?
Jason: And?
迈克:还有,就是我没做.
Mike: And I didn't do it.
杰森:你没做,是说,你没吸,是么?
Jason: You didn't do it as in you did not.
迈克:我没有吸.
Mike: I didn't do the stupid drug.
杰森:那很好,迈克.非常好.
Jason: Well that's great Mike.That's wonderful.
我一直担心,如果你面临那种情形,
I always figured that you'd make that right choice if you had to face
你是不是能做出一个正确的选择,好了,现在我如释重负.
that but I'm relieved.
迈克:爸爸,还没说完.
Mike: Dad, that's not it.
杰森:什么?
Jason: What?
迈克:爸爸,自从那聚会后,我一直在想这件事情.爸爸,我一直开车,开呀开,开呀开……
Mike: Dad, I have been thinking about this since the party.Dad, I have been driving and driving...
杰森:迈克,这事你做得很对.
Jason: Mike, you did the right thing.
迈克:耶,这就是让我疑惑的关键.
Mike: Yeah, that's what kills me.
杰森:我不明白.
Jason: I don't understand.
迈克:爸爸,我知道我没做错,
Mike: Dad, I know I did the right thing.
可是我觉得所有人都会讥笑我,
It's just that I feel like everyone's going to laugh at me.
而且,有一些确实在讥笑.
And some of those people did laugh.
杰森:迈克,你不可能使每一个人都开心的.
Jason: Well, Mike you're not going to be able to please everybody.
迈克:不过,今晚,我让每个人都不开心.
Mike: Yeah well tonight I didn't please anybody.
杰森:除了你自己.
Jason: Except yourself.
迈克:对.
Mike: Yeah.
杰森:对,今晚你做的事情需要真正的勇气,迈克,我非常欣赏你.
Jason: Yeah, what you did tonight took real courage, Mike.I admire you.
迈克:谢谢.
Mike: Thanks.
杰森:再接再厉.
Jason: Sleep on it.
迈克:晚安,爸爸.
Mike: Good night dad.
杰森:晚安,迈克.
Jason: Good night Mike.
迈克:谢谢你爸爸.
Mike: Thanks dad.
杰森:埃迪和鲍纳刚才打电话找你,他们说他俩没去洗手间,而且他们不想去.
Jason: Uh Eddie and boner called for you.They said they didn't go to the bathroom and they don't want to.
迈克:那,你还知道什么?
Mike: Well what do you know?
杰森:什么意思?
Jason: What does that mean?
迈克:很多意思.
Mike: A lot.
杰森:什么世道.迈克:嗨.
Jason: What a world. Mike: Hi.
很多人会告诉你毒品很爽,同样还是这帮人还会告诉你每个人都吸你还会有什么问题.
You know a lot of people tell you that drugs are cool and they're the
可是,他们错了.
same people who are saying that everybody is doing something so what's
并不是所有人都吸,而且你也不必为了爽而去吸.
your problem?Well they're wrong.
听好了,我不是在教训你自己的生活应该怎么过,
Everybody's not doing drugs and you don't have to do it to be cool.
而是在衷告你,你没必要去做一些自己本不想做的事情去迎合朋友们的口味.
Look, I'm not telling you how to live your lives,
还有,毒品也许并不像你原告想的那样爽.
but I am telling you that you don't have to do something that you don't
最后,我说这话,
want to just to keep your friends happy.
没有人会给我钱.这只是我的感受,
I mean, if that's the way that they feel, then maybe they're not your friends.
如果在你看来,这样的说法使我显得很愚钝,
And maybe they're not as cool as you thought they were.And one last thing.
那么,错的是你.
I'm not being paid to say this.
00:20:26,900
This is how I feel and if you think that makes me uncool, then you're wrong.